tatasteel.com 2019-03-28

# Tata Steel Privacy Policy

#### Objective

The purpose of this policy is to maintain the privacy of and protect the personal information of employees, contractors, vendors, interns, associates, customers and business partners of Tata Steel Limited and ensure compliance with laws and regulations applicable (refer annexure A ‘Data Privacy Annexures’ document) to Tata Steel Limited (hereafter referred to as “TSL” or “the organization”).

#### Scope

This policy is applicable to all TSL employees, contractors, vendors, interns, associates, customers and business partners who may receive personal information, have access to personal information collected or processed, or who provide information to the organization.

This Policy applies to all TSL employees, contractors, vendors, interns, associates, customers and business partners who receive personal information from TSL, who have access to personal information collected or processed by TSL, or who provide information to TSL, regardless of geographic location. All employees of TSL are expected to support the privacy policy and principles when they collect and / or handle personal information, or are involved in the process of maintaining or disposing of personal information. This policy provides the information to successfully meet the organization’s commitment towards data privacy.

All partner firms and any Third-Party working with or for TSL, and who have or may have access to personal information, will be expected to have read, understand and comply with this policy. No Third Party may access personal information held by the organization without having first entered into a confidentiality agreement.

Click here to know more
